Hi everyone, welcome to a live stream here on my YouTube.
I didn't know that the audio would be loud in an event venue,
so this is a bit of a surprise.
But hi, live stream here, totally the first time we've been doing that somewhere else
except from home, so it's been really complicated to set up everything here,
to make all the tech work and be on time.
Sorry for the delay, but we're here now.
And without further ado, let me tell you a bit about the venue and the event.
We're here at the Avant-Gadista Munich.
This is a fashion event for alternative fashion.
We'll have a big fashion show in the evening, runway shows with nine designers.
We have an art exhibition, a showroom with all the designers showing their pieces here
in Munich. So next time you're going to plan your trip to Munich, make sure to do it while
Avant-Gadista is taking place. Or if you're from Germany,
come to Munich next time when Avant-Gadista is there.
And in this live stream, I want to show you and introduce you to some brands that are doing a
fashion show here. And I'll start with the first one, the girls from Liquid Disco. Come on, come on.
Sit next to me if you want to go in some way.
Yeah, take me in the middle.
Let me check if the should work.
Testing testing.
Second microphone.
Hi.
Oh, I think it works.
Hello.
Yay.
Hi.
So hi, Elena.
How are you?
Good.
Yeah, a bit stressed out.
How are you?
I'm good.
I think you have to put it closer to your mouth.
Closer to my mouth.
That's very close.
That's what she said.
I feel so colorless next to all of you
because you look amazing and the colors are amazing.
Do you want to tell me a bit about your label and the outfits?
Yeah, sure.
So my label is called Liquid Disco.
I do a lot of colorful outfits
because latex nowadays is black and red.
And I just wanted to do like crazy, fun, rainbow colors.
So that's why I was doing this.
Okay, cool.
So Stephanie and Lara, so nice of you to join us here.
Can you tell me something about your outfit?
I think this is one of the cooler, edgy, happy, colorful outfits from Liquid Disco.
Normally I'm one of those black latex people, obviously.
So Ellen was like, I'll get you the less rainbow one.
I love your outfit and I love the makeup.
Thank you.
But I have to say I also love Ellen's colorful pastel rainbow unicorn outfits a lot.
Colorful pastel unicorn rainbow outfits.
Well, that's quite a description.
But that's really true of what's about the brand.
I try to just use all the colors of the rainbow.
and also do a lot of hand dyed fashion.
As you can see on Lara's outfit,
I try to do a lot of stuff with latex,
like trying to hand dye it in different ways.
Here you can see on Stephanie's outfit,
she's wearing a glitter outfit.
So I'm gluing all the different pieces of glitter,
all of it on myself.
I'm experimenting with latex lace.
That is a lot of work to hand glue
every one of these rhinestones to the outfit.
Yeah, yeah, I'm crazy.
That's what she said.
So you're from Netherlands and you're the first time as a designer at Avant-Guerre.
Is it your first fashion show?
Yes, this is our debut fashion show.
Wow.
Yeah.
So are you excited?
I'm very excited. I think it's going to be very cool.
I have some cool pieces to show and yeah, we're just going to fucking rock.
Obviously.
Yeah.
Are you excited about the show tonight?
I'm super excited to be walking for Elena and wear all these colorful,
cute rainbow unicorn things. The word unicorn is a reoccurring theme in my heart. Unicorn and rainbows, I get it, I get it.
But you've known each other for quite a while already. Yeah, for 10 years maybe.
For like 10 years we've been like modeling and doing stuff in the fetish scene and the reason why I actually started this brand was because I
wanted to wear outfits that were like party wear and also like comfortable so that was I was like
maybe I can make this myself so that's when I was starting liquid disco so you like to wear
latex yourself when you party very much today you're here in your joggers sweatpants like
but at least hey they're colorful it's like of course super matching with your hair and of course
tonight on the catwalk, I'm going to be wearing latex.
Yeah, so I think
the catwalk shows will be
online at the Avant-Guerre-Distart channels
afterwards, so if you miss the fashion shows,
you can still see them, but
obviously...
I said don't miss them. Be there or be square.
Obviously it's cooler to be here in person.
You did
already photo shoots today, I saw.
Yeah, true. I had
another outfit that will be
shown tonight, right, Delon?
Yeah, like it's red, it's super frilly and cute, and I felt super pretty in it.
So yeah, I've been hanging around already.
So what is it here? How would you describe the event?
I really like Avantgardista because it is a high-class fashion event.
It is way more arty than other events that I know.
So there's really space for more than just fetish wear.
we see all these amazing brands
with corsets, glitters,
mirrors, all the things.
There's space for everybody. I love it.
But it's also a cool
place to just hang around and see
everyone again because we've been
meeting here for years already.
After COVID, we've missed everybody.
Where has everybody been? And now
everybody can see each other again. It's just so nice
to be familiar with everybody.
That's true. Ladies, can you
stand up and turn around and show your
outfits again?
You can choose two if you want to.
So it's a two-piece.
Can you tell me something about the individual outfits?
Yeah, so Lara is wearing a piece from the Synesthesia collection.
It's a hand-dyed outfit.
So the latex is meant to be empowering.
It's meant to be giving you like a badass feel that you feel like that you want to rock.
And you just feel comfortable and good in it.
and Stephanie is wearing a piece from my collection that I will be presenting on
Boris K in Antwerp in December oh wow so another fashion show in December yeah we're going hard
um so she's wearing like a signature beret style with a dream body suit and a peplum belt
all uh with little bit little bit of beatings and she looks very fucking cute in it so I'm happy
It's gorgeous. You look both look gorgeous. So let me check with the
regime about the time I
See you too. I don't know what that means
We need to do two more questions or questions to my mother
Ask you a question or go ahead
What are you most excited for this weekend, oh
I don't know. I have to host the fashion shows tonight. So wow, this is a bit of
excitement for me. Obviously, I don't want to forget something when I talk about the labels. I'll be
introducing you tonight as well on the catwalk.
You're a professional, so I trust you. I hope so. We'll see. We'll make the best out of it. All right. Thanks for being here.
Thanks for stopping by. Thank you so much. Thank you, girls.
And I will see you tonight on the catwalk. We'll have a drink afterwards, obviously. Of course, of course. Thank you so much.
All right, my first guests, Liquid Disco, but I have the next ones waiting already.
They're from Poland and ETA.
So please just come on and join me so we don't let people wait.
Yes, sit next to me. I'll give you the microphone.
Thank you.
Go in the middle. You can sit on the...
Oh my God, this looks so gorgeous.
Hi.
Hi. Thank you for joining me.
Thank you for reminding us.
I think you have to put it a bit closer to your mouth.
So, Eteri Shop.
Yeah, right.
I practiced.
Thank you very much.
From Poland.
Yes.
And you're doing a lot of cost.
Oh, you already turned it on.
Yeah, it's very easy.
You just need to press one button and it will turn on.
Actually, you can press this button to change these effects.
You can try.
Oh, I can press the button here.
Yeah.
Oh, nice.
Moreover, you can program your effects, you can program your text.
Oh wow.
So you're doing like costumes for stage outfit, for performers.
Yeah, that's actually right for event agencies, for different parties who like to rave and
DJs, performers, acrobats and every kind of artist actually.
Video clips you said.
And you're focusing on LED on the one hand, but also on mirror outfits.
Yeah, even costumes combining both mirrors and LEDs and it looks really cool.
Unfortunately, we didn't bring them with us, but yes, we can combine not only just mirror or just LED, so everything.
That is so unique. I love the design.
Thank you. This is acrylic mirror. It's totally safe and it weighs less than real mirror, but it looks exactly like real mirror.
real mirror. So it's totally safe and perfect for outfits for artists and performers. Wow,
okay. I can imagine that it's quite warm in the outfit. No, I'm speaking English. Yeah,
but it's warm enough. It's very warm. I mean, I'm sweating here in the spotlight. I can't
imagine how you're sweating. Yeah, a bit of air, finally. But you've been at the Evangelista
So before already.
For us, for three of us, it's the first time.
But we've been here two times before as Eteri Shop.
This is our third time.
Our actual designers didn't manage to come, but we're here.
They are with us.
They're in spirit here.
I worked for a terry shop at the Evangelista 2019.
Yeah, so I've been one of your models.
So it's really fun to have you here.
And I think you will be wearing our dress this evening.
I'll be wearing tonight for hosting the fashion shows.
I'll be wearing an etere dress with a mirror outfit.
So it's a floor-length dress, mirrors everywhere.
I tried it on yesterday. It's gorgeous.
And you are as well.
thank you
I loved your yesterday's outfit
a lot but I didn't have time
to tell you that
it's amazing
I'm really looking forward to the show tonight
to wear this outfit, it's really unique
and I love that you
made it again this year to Munich
thank you
are you often in Germany?
no
just for us
especially for this event
And like our special opportunity to come to Munich and to see Germany a little bit.
To meet our designers and express ourselves and to show the world what we are doing and what it's possible to create with allergies and mirror.
And that it can be worn even in everyday life.
As you can see.
I was just about to say that.
I mean, the costumes are really impressive, but I can imagine that not everyone wants to walk around every day dressed like this.
You can combine it with something.
So you're wearing a bustier?
Yeah, it's a corset.
Can you stand up and turn around so everyone can see it?
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
You can combine it with the white shirt and make it an amazing evening outfit.
And should I take this one so you can stand up?
And you can show your outfit, what you're wearing.
It's a really cute harness.
So, I mean, if you just look in here,
like here, or there.
And you can see yourself in the mirror if you need.
Yes, it's like pretty versatile,
and you can wear it the way you like it, so.
It's really cute.
I mean, you can upgrade every outfit with that,
and it's just, well, it's really heavy.
I didn't know.
It's made for men, yeah.
Obviously because I wouldn't be able to hold it all the time.
Okay.
Wow.
So what does the time say?
Are we good?
Okay.
Then thank you for being here.
Thank you very much.
We'll see each other tonight.
See you in the amazing dress.
You have to help me into the dress because I can't do it alone.
But I can't help you.
Thank you for stopping by.
Have fun today.
I'll take that.
Bye.
The water!
Wow, this has been gorgeous so far. I love the outfits. I love the girls.
Maybe... which camera is it? Oh my god, this is so professional today.
Because I have two cameras, I have a microphone. I've never worked this professional before, so to say.
to say and there are photographers. Wow, thank you guys for supporting me. Also to the tech guys and
everyone here, the crew, thank you. You make me feel important and professional but maybe you
notice that my outfit is quite nice but my shoes are not that nice. So I'll have someone joining me
which you probably know from my previous videos who will bring me some shoes. So please come on.
Yeah, you.
Hi.
Hello.
How do you do?
You stand up and come down?
I think the camera is meant for sitting.
Yay.
Sit here.
You can sit in the chair and you can join me.
Yeah.
Please take your microphone.
I brought you some boots.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
So you have to talk now while I'm going to change shoes.
I'm going to help you with that.
That's my job.
Otherwise, I can't watch this.
If you're a professional and you watch amateurs doing something, it's not gonna work.
You think I'm an amateur untying my shoes?
You're pretty good for an amateur.
I do this every day, you know.
Well, amateur comes from loving something.
Yeah, I love tying my shoes.
But it's kind of difficult with a microphone, so I respect that.
Yeah, I'm a woman, I can do both at once.
So maybe you know that we're already a bit familiar, we've seen each other before.
We did some videos before we know each other from countless fairs and events from Avangardestars.
Do you want to put on the shoes now, Oleg?
Yes, but then maybe...
She's going to take on the video.
Can you hold the microphone?
Then please tell me something about yourself.
He brought you and now he's sitting in front of your shoes.
Alright, can you tell me something about the shoes you're wearing?
The shoes I'm wearing, the boots, they are the most sexiest boots alive.
Because they're made from Fernando Berlin.
They're beautiful, shiny, and you can match it with everything.
So that's what I can say.
So it's PVC, patent leather?
it's vinyl on the outside and the inside is leather. Yes. And they're over knee and
I love that they're like pointed. Yes. And I saw that you put a boot band over it
which really glitters so the rhinestones. Thank you. This is confusing. I think the
Boots demand the golden chair.
Yeah, they look great.
Although, I have to say,
a golden boot band would look good with a golden chair.
Yes.
I have to switch again.
No, no, that's fine.
That's fine.
We're at the point where we're saying,
no more changes.
It's got to go like that.
Can you tell me something about your show tonight?
About my show tonight?
Yes, we have...
Our topic is strong women.
This is our topic for tonight.
and we have very very different outfits and very different boots so we want to
present the diversity how you can match boots, how you can wear boots and that
they're not just one dimensional piece of fashion and we're very very excited
about it. Cool, so I'm wearing matching heels to my outfit like with silver. What
What outfit are you going to wear tonight?
I will wear the very high, I don't know how you have to say which one, you better describe
the boots, not me, but I have a beautiful black catsuit and over it I have, you will
see beautiful nice boots.
She's going to present our boot model for the fans out there, for the Berlin fans, our
boot model 101. That's the name of them. And it's a boot from our Divine
selection. Within our old collection we have a Divine selection
which is a bit more, let's say, they're a bit over the top. A bit over the top. Over the top is good.
I mean, you're at the right place here to be over the top because we have the fashion show events.
Yes, exactly. So we have like our regular boots which we always try to be
stay very simple and simple in design so to speak and where we say less is more
and then there's a divine selection. I mean she already is divine. That's true exactly.
Can you stand up and like turn around once so we can see the overall outfit
because I love also the look with the leather leggings and the simplicity with
the white top that you just put on top of it. So it's really cool outfit also
for every day I would say. Depends on your day I guess. I would wear it every day.
Would you wear it to the office or to work? I'm an artist so I can do whatever
I want. If you're an artist it's an everyday art. That's what I say you know
when people ask me is this an everyday but depends on your everyday you know
it's it differs a lot. Yeah well the good thing about my work is that my
colleagues don't mind how I show up so I think if I would wear this to the office
they would be like oh okay nice and then it would be over again so they don't
mind what I'm wearing which I'm really grateful for. And it really depends on
the organization where you work and I don't know if you walk a lot you know if
you of course if you walk a lot maybe they want to be a bit more conservative
on the heel but other than that you know it depends on how you combine it that's
I think always the most important thing. It's a good training for your back
muscles. If you have a lot of high heels on, then after a time you get really that
straight. So are you like experienced with high heels? Do you wear them often?
Yes, I do. I do, but still every boot has its own way how it feels to walk on, so
that's practice and then you get into it. Where are you from by the way? I'm from
Germany. Okay, so we could talk basically we talk German with everyone except for
the first two designers, but I could talk to you in German. Okay, I thought this was
the general concept here.
It is.
No, it is the concept here
because the viewers
are so international
so we do this in English.
I just heard they were
talking to them in English
but I didn't think
that they maybe
were in German.
I think we could do
but then most of the viewers
wouldn't understand it
because they're international.
So we're going to stick
with English.
So also thanks to you
because your English
is also very good.
I'm always glad
that people can join me
in English.
You do a good job.
Thank you.
So are you excited for
is it your first show tonight?
At Avant-Garde Isto, yes.
I walk more often on fashion shows, but in this way, it's my first time.
And with this great, lovely, sexy boots, it's also my first time.
In public.
Really?
In public, yeah.
Nice.
So, I don't know.
I think my producer just ran off.
We're just going to sit here and talk.
So, we're just going to sit here and talk until they're ready,
because I have another designer joining.
In fact, you're wearing leggings from the next designer joining me.
I just saw that.
One minute? Okay. You've been here every time since the Avogadro set takes place.
Yes. Why do you always come back? In a good way. They forced me to.
There are several reasons. First of all, I like the whole concept that this is a
bit more really a fashion event. You know, when we do events, a lot of them are
pop-up stores and fairs of course. And here it's really more about the art,
which I really really enjoy. And the atmosphere is a bit different.
Of course it's super nice to have a fashion show as a fashion brand and that
we have this platform where we can really present in a high quality stuff,
in a high quality setting, our creations is very nice, is very very good.
So we always glad to come back.
Yeah, so I know that you're also on social media.
I'll of course link everything in the description text.
Would you describe this as a Fittish event or how would you describe this event?
Good question.
I think the beauty there of it is that it's mixed.
Of course, it's somehow fetish,
but I think it's more and more getting into the normal way.
So with the fashion show, it's really professional.
So of course, the designs, it's a kink,
but at the same time, I think it's...
Yeah, somehow it's mixed.
Of course, it is.
I think what's really important to say is that you really see
that the name Avogadista wasn't chosen randomly.
but you can see a lot of people here who do something at first
and then sometime later you see it in Paris.
That happens.
So I'm not kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Because here we really can experiment.
Here are people who are really in love with what they do
and they come up with the random things that are sometimes absolutely mind-boggling.
The designs I've seen here are really something else.
They're so unique.
Yeah, so you can really see new things here.
This is really nice.
Okay, so let me check if the next ones are already.
I have to put on a coat, but I can already say thank you to you.
Oh no, the water.
I think we have to put the water somewhere else.
Everyone is falling over it.
So I hope you had fun so far and could get an idea about what Avant-Gadista is about.
This camera is okay. Oh my god, the sun is shining directly into the windows above me
and so everyone else in front of me is like totally facing the sun which is not really nice.
I'm sorry guys. But are you ready for the next one? Yes? Are you ready? Then come on, join me guys.
I don't mind
then sit down next to me
you can sit down here
oh no
I just said
I just said it two minutes ago
I just said it
yeah you can come closer no worries
so I will give you
the microphone I'm going to switch to German
in a sec let me just introduce you first
Yeah. So this is Benno von Stein. You also should know him from my channel because I visited him in his
atelier and I've been doing a collection try on so we're all friends by now.
But nevertheless, he showed me something new today and I already love the gold leggings here sitting
next to me, but I'm going to switch to German now because you're like German, German, how
do you call it?
Now I don't, now I already missed the English words.
You see my brain already switched to German.
No, I was just about to say you're a German native speaker.
Hi.
I will, don't worry, I'll translate in between to English so you guys don't miss anything.
Schön, dass du da bist.
Celine, thank you for the invitation to be here on the...
On the golden chair.
Which means the world, right?
Yes, and you have your pretty lady, Haidani, by the way.
You have something nice on.
Can you stand up and explain?
Yes, and for our fashion show today I have come up with something special.
I am a little flashed because the topic of gold was also taken up behind me.
Yes, everything is gold today.
I didn't know that before.
And I had this strass made because it's made of gold aluminum.
And I have leggings for that.
Can I turn you around?
So he just had the accessories made.
With a very nice, character-emphasized cut, as you can see.
Okay, let me just translate for a sec.
So you just had the accessories made because you needed them in gold.
Oh, here's the tech.
Always.
And the leggings are new as well in gold with the cut that really emphasizes your beautiful figure.
Just leave it. It's okay.
And she's wearing a corset and a coat.
What's up with this coat? I don't think I've seen that before.
Yes, for the Avant-Garde fashion show I always have a very specific new idea.
and I always had the coat theme in the shows,
but this time I have sewn a coat for every model for my run, Benno von Stein.
Men like women.
This will be my biggest presentation of all the designs that I will be selling next year.
Biggest fashion. And they are all going to be available for sale next year.
So you present them tonight and from then on they can be purchased.
This is a secret preview. Secret preview, yeah.
As we designers always talk about. Yes.
Did you sew everything yourself in the previous weeks? I heard you sewed for a very long time and a lot?
Yes, in the two and a half weeks I had left for the preparation, I made 21 new designs.
Coats, jewelry, new corset belts, new stylings for the gold series, which you will see on the Modenschau for men and women.
The theme is always black plus color, this time it's black plus gold.
And the title of the work, when I couldn't do it anymore, was Goldfinger.
I'm just joining you. I'm not walking tonight. I'm in charge of the bondage stage tonight
But it's so nice of you to join. Yes. I'm very happy to be here and it feels really great and it looks great
I'm very happy that I'm allowed to wear it. So it was really a spontaneous
Thing spontaneous. Yes. I
Know that you've been running around you. I need a model. I need a model
But we had worked together for years. Yeah. Yeah
That's also the thing about here that everyone is like a big family.
We've known each other all for ages.
It's always nice to see each other.
What can you say about the Amagatis?
You've been here as well all the time.
I'm here since the beginning.
And I'm really happy to be here like every year
because it's really an outstanding event
where you can meet all the people you like,
where you can wear nice dresses and everything,
where you can just show your kink.
So I'm really happy to be here.
Okay.
So I think we had a lot of information packed into the last half hour.
And I think we're done now because we have to get back to rehearsals and fittings and selling.
Because there's also the showroom here, which everyone can stop by and try on the designs from the designers.
Designs? Designers?
Yeah.
So again, check out Amagadista.
Check out the social media channels.
As I said, I'll link every label I've shown you here before.
Thanks for everyone stopping by.
Thanks to the tech guys.
And I think that's it for today.
I'm going to get out of this heat here now and have a drink.
I think I'll see every one of you.
I don't know which camera it is.
Who of you is it?
Are you?
Okay, I think we'll see everyone.
Bye.
See you next time.